Sculpture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- United States (Box 17)
  - Artists Known (Box 17)
    - Bowen, Gaza, act.c.1978 (Box 18)
    - Bourgeois, Louise, 1911- (Box 18)
      - To 1959 (Box 18)
      - 1960-1969 (Box 18)
      - 1970-1979 [Slide boxes 106-107] (Box 18)
        - Body Parts performance [Slide box 107] (Box 18)
      - 1980-1989 (Box 18)
    - Brackett, Edward Augustus, 1918-1908 (Box 18)
    - Braderman, Joan, 1948- (Box 18)
    - Brecht, George, 1925- (Box 18)
    - Brevik, Bard (Box 18)
    - Brisley, Staurt, 1933- (Box 18)
    - Brockley, Joanne (Box 18)
    - Browere, John Henri I., 1792-1834 (Box 18)
    - Brown, Henry Kirke, 1814-1886 (Box 18)
    - Brown, Roger, 1941- (Box 18)
    - Buchanan, Bervely, 1940- (Box 18)
    - Bufano, Beniamino (Box 18)
    - Burden, Chris, 1946- [Slide boxes 107-108] (Box 18)
    - Burke, Selma Hortese, 1907- [Slide box 108] (Box 18)
    - Burns, Mark (Box 18)
    - Burton, Scott, 1939-1989 (Box 18)
      Xx Sculpture U.S.-Armajani, Siah
    - Butler, David, 1898- (Box 18)
    - Butter, Tom (Box 18)
    - Butterfield, Deborah (Box 18)
    - Byars, James Lee, 1932- (Box 18)
    - Caesar, Doris (Box 18)
    - Cage, John, 1912-1992 (Box 18)
    - Calder, Alexander, 1898-1976 (Box 18)
      - Mobiles [Slide box 109] (Box 19)
      - Stabiles (Box 19)
        - Stegosaurus (Box 19)
      - Wire Constructions (Box 19)
      - Wood (Box 19)
    - Calder, A. Stirling, 1870-1945 (Box 19)
    - Callery, Mary, 1903- (Box 19)
    - Campoli, Cosmo, 1923- (Box 19)
    - Caparin, Rhys, 1909- (Box 19)
    - Carlson, Cynthia, 1942- (Box 19)
    - Carman, Nancy, 1950- (Box 19)
    - Casebere, James, 1953- (Box 19)
    - Castanis, Muriel, 1928- (Box 19)
    - Catlett, Elizabeth, 1919- (Box 19)
    - Cavallito, Albino (Box 19)
    - Celmins, Vija, 1939- (Box 19)
    - Chamberlain, John, 1927- (Box 19)
      - Before-1969 (Box 19)
      - 1961-1963 (Box 19)
      - 1964-1965 [Slide box 110] (Box 19)
      - 1966-1969 (Box 19)
      - 1970- (Box 19)
    - Chase-Riboud, Barbara Dewayne, 1939- (Box 19)
    - Cheang, Shu Lea, 1954- (Box 19)
    - Chicago, Judy, 1939- (Box 19)
      - The Dinner Party (Box 19)
    - Chryssa, 1933- (Box 19)
    - Clevenger, Shobal Vail, 1812-1843 (Box 19)
    - Connelly, Arch (Box 19)
    - Conner, Bruce, 1933- (Box 19)
    - Connor, Maureen, 1947- [Slide box 111] (Box 19)
    - Conwill, Houston, 1947- (Box 19)
    - Cook, Robert (Box 19)
    - Cornell, Joseph, 1903- (Box 19)
    - Corner, Philip, 1933- (Box 19)
    - Coyne, Petah, 1953- (Box 19)
    - Crawford, Thomas, 1813-1857 (Box 19)
      X Crawford, Thomas & Rinehart, William H.
    - Daley, William, 1925- (Box 19)
    - Dallin, Cyrus Edwin, 1861- (Box 19)
    - Damon, Betsy, 1940- (Box 19)
    - Daphnis, Nassos, 1914- (Box 19)
    - Davidson, Jo, 1883- (Box 19)
    - Davies, Arthur B., 1862-1928 (Box 19)
    - Davis, Emma Lu, 1905- (Box 19)
    - De Andrea, John Louis, 1941- (Box 19)
    - De Creeft, Jose, 1884- [Slide box 112] (Box 19)
    - DeFazio, John, 1941- (Box 19)
    - DeKooning, Willem, 1904- (Box 19)
    - De Lap, Tony (Box 19)
    - De Maria, Walter, 1935- (Box 19)
    - Demetrios, A., 1932- (Box 19)
    - Denes, Agnes, 1938- (Box 19)
    - Dennis, Donna, 1942- (Box 19)
    - Der Harootian, Koren (Box 19)
    - De Rivera, Jose, 1904- (Box 19)
    - DeStaebler, Stephen, 1933- (Box 19)
    - Diedrich, Wilhelm Hunt, 1884- (Box 19)
    - Diller, Elizabeth, 1964- (Box 19)
    - Dine, Jim, 1935- (Box 19)
      X Dine, James
    - Dion, M. & J. Simon (Box 19)
    - Di Suvero, Mark, 1933- (Box 19)
      - Before-1962 (Box 19)
      - 1963-1969 [Slide boxes 112-113] (Box 19)
      - 1970- [Slide box 113] (Box 19)
    - Dodge, Charles J., 1806-1886 (Box 19)
    - Dogg, John (Box 19)
    - Dos Santos, Judite, 1945- (Box 19)
    - Douke, Daniel (Box 19)
    - Downey, Juan (Box 19)
    - Doyle, Alexander, 1857-1922 (Box 19)
    - Doyle, Tom, 1928- (Box 19)
    - Duble, Lu, 1896- (Box 19)
    - Duff, John (Box 19)
    - Duran, Robert (Box 19)
    - Durham, Jimmie, 1940- (Box 19)
    - Dzubas, Friedel (Box 19)
    - Eakins, Thomas, 1844-1916 (Box 19)
    - Eckart, Christian (Box 19)
    - Edelson, Mary Beth, act.c. 1970- (Box 19)
    - Edmondson, William, 1870-1951 [Slide boxes 113-114] (Box 19)
    - Edwards, Melvin, 1937- [Slide box 114] (Box 19)
    - Erickson, Kate & Mel Ziegler (Box 19)
    - Esherick, Wharton, 1887- (Box 19)
    - Eversley, Frederick John, 1941- (Box 19)
    - Ewing, Lauren (Box 19)
    - Faggi, Alfeo, 1885- (Box 19)
    - Ferber, Herbert, 1906- (Box 19)
    - Ferrara, Jackie, 1929- (Box 19)
    - Ferren, John, 1905- (Box 19)
    - Ferrer, Rafael [Slide box 115] (Box 20)
    - Fessler, Ann (Box 20)
    - Fine, Jud (Box 20)
    - Fisher, R.M., 1947- (Box 20)
    - Fisher, Joel, 1947- (Box 20)
    - Flannagan, John, 1895-1942 (Box 20)
    - Flavin, Dan, 1933- (Box 20)
    - Fleischner, Richard [Slide box 116] (Box 20)
    - Forakis, Peter, 1927- (Box 20)
    - Fox, Judy (Box 20)
    - Frank, Mary (Box 20)
    - Frank, Regina, 1965- (Box 20)
    - Fraser, James Earle, 1876-1953 (Box 20)
    - Frazee, John, 1790-1852 (Box 20)
    - Frazier, Charles, 1922- (Box 20)
    - Frazier, Paul, 1922- (Box 20)
    - French, Daniel Chester, 1850-1931 (Box 20)
    - Frey, Viola (Box 20)
    - Fried, Nancy, 1945- (Box 20)
    - Friedman, Ken, act.c.1966-1968 (Box 20)
    - Fuller, Meta V.W., 1877-1968 [Slide boxes 116-117] (Box 20)
      X Fuller, Meta Vaux or Fuller, Meta Warrick
    - Fuller, Sue, 1914- [Slide box 117] (Box 20)
    - Gallo, Frank, 1914- (Box 20)
    - Garet, Jedd, 1955- (Box 20)
    - Geis, William R. III, 1940- (Box 20)
    - Getz, Ilse, 1917- (Box 20)
    - Gilhooly, David (Box 20)
    - Gillette & Schneider, 1941- (Box 20)
    - Ginnever, Charles (Box 20)
    - Glasco, Joseph, 1925- (Box 20)
    - Glenny, Anna, 1888- (Box 20)
    - Gober, Robert, 1954- (Box 20)
    - Goings, Ralph, 1928- (Box 20)
    - Goldberg, Michael, 1924- (Box 20)
    - Golub, Leon, 1922- (Box 20)
    - Gonzalez-Torres, Felix, 1957- [Slide boxes 117-118] (Box 20)
    - Gordin, Sidney, 1918- [Slide box 118] (Box 20)
    - Gorky, Arshile, 1904-1948 (Box 20)
    - Goto, Joseph, 1916- (Box 20)
    - Gottlieb, Adolph, 1903- (Box 20)
    - Gould, Thomas R., 1818-1881 (Box 20)
    - Grafly, Charles, 1862-1929 (Box 20)
    - Graham, Daniel H., 1942- (Box 20)
    - Graham, Robert, 1938- (Box 20)
    - Graves, Nancy, 1940-1995 (Box 20)
    - Gray, David, 1927- (Box 20)
    - Green, Jasha (Box 20)
    - Green, Renee, 1959- (Box 20)
    - Green, Vanalyne, 1948- (Box 20)
    - Greenbaum, Dorothea, 1893- (Box 20)
    - Greenough, Horatio, 1805-1852 [Slide boxes 118-119] (Box 20)
    - Grippe, Peter, 1912- [Slide box 119] (Box 20)
    - Grooms, Red, 1937- (Box 20)
    - Gross, Chaim, 1904- (Box 20)
    - Grossman, Nancy, 1940- (Box 20)
    - Grosvenor, Robert (Box 20)
    - Group Material, act. 1979 (Box 20)
    - Haacke, Hans Christoph, 1936- (Box 20)
    - Hacker, David (Box 20)
    - Hadzi, Dimitri, 1929- (Box 20)
    - Hague, Raoul, 1904- (Box 20)
    - Hamilton, Ann, 1956- (Box 20)
    - Hammond, Harmony Lynn, 1944- (Box 20)
    - Hammons, David, 1943- (Box 20)
    - Hampton, James, 1909-1964 [Slide boxes 119-120] (Box 20)
    - Hansen, James [Slide box 120] (Box 20)
    - Hanson, Duane, 1925-1996 (Box 20)
    - Hardy, Tom, 1921- (Box 20)
    - Hare, David, 1917- [Slide boxes 120-121] (Box 20)
    - Haring, Keith, 1958-1990 [Slide box 121] (Box 21)
    - Harkavy, Minna, 1895- (Box 21)
    - Harries, Mags, 1945- (Box 21)
    - Harris, Paul, 1925- (Box 21)
    - Harrison, Newton, 1932- (Box 21)
    - Harrison, Rachel, 1966- (Box 21)
    - Hart, Frederick (Box 21)
    - Harvey, Bessie, 1928- (Box 21)
    - Haseltine, James H., 1833-1907 (Box 21)
    - Hassinger, Maren, 1947- (Box 21)
    - Hatch, Connie (Box 21)
    - Hawkinson, Tim, 1960- (Box 21)
    - Hebald, Milton, 1917- (Box 21)
    - Hedrick, Wally (Box 21)
    - Heizer, Michael, 1944- (Box 21)
      - 1967 (Box 21)
      - 1968 (Box 21)
      - 1969 (Box 21)
      - 1970- (Box 21)
    - Hendricks, Geoffrey, 1931- (Box 21)
    - Herms, George (Box 21)
    - Hesse, Eve (Box 21)
      Xx Sculpture Germany
    - Hicks, Sheila (Box 21)
    - Higgins, Dick, 1938-1998 [Slide box 122] (Box 21)
    - Higgins, Edward (Box 21)
    - Highstein, Jene (Box 21)
    - Hill, Gary, 1951- (Box 21)
    - Hinman, Charles (Box 21)
    - Hoffman, Malvina, 1887- (Box 21)
      Xx Africa Central- Mangbetu Woman
    - Holt, Nancy Louise, 1938- (Box 21)
    - Holzer, Jenny, 1950- (Box 21)
    - Hooks, Earl J., 1927- (Box 21)
    - Hord, Donal, 1902- (Box 21)
    - Horn, Roni (Box 21)
    - Hosmer, Harriet Goodhue, 1830-1908 [Slide boxes 122-123] (Box 21)
    - How, Kenneth, 1833- [Slide box 123] (Box 21)
    - Howard, Robert, 1896- (Box 21)
    - Hsieh, Teching (Box 21)
    - Hudson, Robert, 1938- (Box 21)
    - Huebler, Douglas, 1924- (Box 21)
    - Hughto, Margie, 1944- (Box 21)
    - Hunt, Bryan, 1947- (Box 21)
    - Hunt, Richard Howard, 1935- (Box 21)
    - Hunt, William Morris (Box 21)
    - Hurson, Michael, 1925- (Box 21)
    - Hutchinson, Peter (Box 21)
    - Icaro, Paolo (Box 21)
    - Indiana, Robert, 1928- (Box 21)
    - Insley, William, 1929- (Box 21)
    - Irwin, Robert, 1928- (Box 21)
    - Israel, Margaret, 1929- (Box 21)
    - Ives, Chauncy B., 1810-1894 (Box 21)
    - Jackson, May Howard, 1877-1931 (Box 21)
    - Jackson-Jarves, Martha, 1952- (Box 21)
    - Jaffe, Lee (Box 21)
    - Jemison, G. Peter, 1945- (Box 21)
    - Jenney, Neil, 1945- (Box 21)
    - Jess (Box 21)
    - Jimenez, Luis Alfonso Jr., 1940- (Box 21)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1930- [Slide boxes 123-124] (Box 21)
    - Johnson, Don [Slide box 124] (Box 21)
    - Johnson, Sargent Claude, 1887-1967 (Box 21)
    - Jonas, Joan, 1936- (Box 21)
    - Jones and Ginzel (Box 21)
    - Jones, Benjamin, 1942- (Box 21)
    - Jones, Kim (Box 21)
    - Jones, Philip Mallory, 1947- (Box 21)
    - Jones, Ronald (Box 21)
    - Judd, Donald, 1928-1994 (Box 21)
      - Chinati Foundation, Marfa, Texas (Box 21)
      - 1961-1965 (Box 21)
      - 1966-1967 [Slide box 125] (Box 21)
      - 1968 (Box 21)
      - 1969 (Box 21)
      - 1970- (Box 21)
    - Kadish, Reuben, 1913- (Box 21)
    - Kahn, Tobi (Box 21)
    - Kaish, Luise, 1925- (Box 21)
    - Kalish, Howard (Box 21)
    - Kaltenbach, Steve (Box 21)
    - Kanayama, Akira, 1924- (Box 21)
    - Kaprow, Allan, 1927- (Box 21)
    - Kauffman, Craig (Box 21)
    - Kaufman, Jane, act.c.1979 [Slide boxes 125-126] (Box 21)
    - Kauppi, Tauno, 1926- [Slide box 126] (Box 21)
    - Kaz, Nathanial, 1917- (Box 21)
    - Keister, Steve (Box 21)
    - Kelley, Mike, 1954- (Box 21)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1923- (Box 21)
      - Comparison (Box 21)
      - Before-1960 (Box 21)
      - 1961- (Box 21)
    - Kendrick, Mel, 1949- (Box 21)
    - Kent, Adaline, 1900-1957 (Box 21)
    - Kessler, Jon, 1957- (Box 21)
    - Kienholz, Edward, 1927-1994 [Slide box 127] (Box 22)
    - Kim, Byron, 1961- (Box 22)
    - Kim, William, 1925- (Box 22)
    - Kipp, Lyman, 1929- (Box 22)
    - Kitson, Henry, 1865-1947 (Box 22)
    - Kohn, Gabriel, 1910- (Box 22)
    - Koons, Jeff, 1955- [Slide boxes 127-128] (Box 22)
    - Kosuth, Joseph, 1945- [Slide box 128] (Box 22)
    - Kramer, Reuben Robert, 1909- (Box 22)
    - Kreis, Henry, 1899- (Box 22)
    - Knowles, Alison, 1933- (Box 22)
    - Kruger, Louise, 1924- (Box 22)
    - Kuehn, Gary (Box 22)
    - Kuehn, George, 1944- (Box 22)
    - Kuriloff, Aaron, 1929- (Box 22)
    - Kushner, Robert, 1949- (Box 22)
    - Lachaise, Gaston, 1882-1935 (Box 22)
    - Lacy, Suzanne, 1945- (Box 22)
    - Laing, Gerald (Box 22)
    - Langager, Craig (Box 22)
    - Lanigan-Schmidt, T. (Box 22)
    - Lankton, Greer, 1958- (Box 22)
    - Lantz, Michael (Box 22)
    - Lasch, Pat, 1944- (Box 22)
    - Lassaw, Ibram, 1913- (Box 22)
    - Laurent, Robert, 1890- (Box 22)
    - Lawler, Louise, 1947- [Slide boxes 128-129] (Box 22)
    - Lawrie, Lee [Slide box 129] (Box 22)
    - Lee, Arthur, 1881- (Box 22)
    - Leibowitz, Cary S., 1963- (Box 22)
    - Lekberg, Barbara, 1925- (Box 22)
    - Lemieux, Annette (Box 22)
    - Leonard, Zoe, 1961- (Box 22)
    - Leone & Macdonald (Box 22)
    - Le Parc (Box 22)
    - Le Va, Barry, 1941- (Box 22)
    - Levine, Les, 1936- (Box 22)
    - Levine, Marilyn (Box 22)
    - Levine, Sherrie, 1947- (Box 22)
    - Lewis, Edmonia, 1845-1900 (Box 22)
    - Leewis III, Joseph, 1953- (Box 22)
    - LeWitt, Sol, 1928- (Box 22)
      - Before-1966 (Box 22)
      - 1967-1969 (Box 22)
      - 1970- [Slide boxes 129-130] (Box 22)
    - Liberman, Alexander, 1912- [Slide box 130] (Box 22)
    - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1923- (Box 22)
    - Lightfoot, Cathy (Box 22)
    - Lin, Maya Ying, 1959- (Box 22)
      Xx Architecture U.S.
    - Lipovsky, Marvin (Box 22)
    - Lippold, Richard, 1915- (Box 22)
    - Lipski, Donald, 1947- (Box 22)
    - Lipton, Seymour, 1903- (Box 22)
    - Little, Ken (Box 22)
    - Lobe, Robert, 1945- (Box 22)
    - Lopez, Jose Dolores, 1868-1938 (Box 22)
    - Lopez, Yolanda M., 1942- (Box 22)
    - Love, Ed, 1936- (Box 22)
    - Lucero, Michael (Box 22)
    - Lucier, Mary (Box 22)
    - Luna, James, 1950- (Box 22)
    - Lundberg, Bill (Box 22)
    - Lye, Len, 1901 (Box 22)
    - Lysohir, Marilyn (Box 22)
    - McCarthy, Paul, 1945- [Slide boxes 130-131] (Box 22)
    - McCollum, Allan [Slide box 131] (Box 22)
    - MacConnel, Kim, 1946- (Box 22)
    - McCracken, John Harvey, 1934- (Box 22)
    - McIntire, Samuel, 1757-1811 (Box 22)
    - Maciunas, George, 1931-1978 (Box 22)
    - MacMonnies, Frederick, 1863-1934 (Box 22)
    - MacNeil, Hermon, 1866-1947 (Box 22)
    - Magnuson, Ann (Box 22)
    - Madsen, Loren (Box 22)
    - Maduna, Vusumuzi, 1940- (Box 22)
    - Malderelli, Oronzio, 1892- (Box 22)
    - Mallary, Robert, 1917- (Box 22)
    - Man Ray, 1890-1976 [Slide boxes 131-132] (Box 22)
    - Manship, Paul, 1885-1966 [Slide box 132] (Box 22)
    - Margulis, Berta, 1907- (Box 22)
    - Marisol Escobar, 1930- (Box 22)
    - Martinez, Daniel Joseph, 1957- (Box 22)
    - Mason, John, 1927- (Box 22)
    - Matta-Clark, Gordon, 1943-1978 (Box 22)
    - Mayer, Rosemary [Slide box 133] (Box 23)
    - Meadmore, Clement (Box 23)
    - Merz, Marisa (Box 23)
    - Mesa-Bains, Amalia, 1943- (Box 23)
    - Mihail (Box 23)
    - Mikowski, Antoni, 1935- (Box 23)
    - Miller, Brenda, 1941- (Box 23)
    - Miller, John, 1954- (Box 23)
    - Mills, Clark, 1815-1883 (Box 23)
    - Milmore, Martin, 1844-1883 (Box 23)
    - Miss, Mary, 1944- (Box 23)
      - 1966-1970 (Box 23)
      - 1971-1975 (Box 23)
      - 1976-1980 (Box 23)
      - 1981- (Box 23)
    - Mitchell, Tyrone, 1944- (Box 23)
    - Moffat, Donald, 1955- (Box 23)
    - Monroe, Keith, 1917- (Box 23)
    - Montanez Ortiz, Rafael, 1934- (Box 23)
    - Montano, Linda (Box 23)
      Xx Sculpture U.S. -Hsieh, Teching
    - Morrel, Marc (Box 23)
    - Morris, Robert, 1931- [Slide box 134] (Box 23)
      - 1961 (Box 23)
      - 1962 (Box 23)
      - 1963 (Box 23)
      - 1964 (Box 23)
      - 1965 (Box 23)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 23)
      - 1968 (Box 23)
      - 1969 (Box 23)
      - 1970-1979 [Slide boxes 134-135] (Box 23)
      - 1980- [Slide box 135] (Box 23)
    - Morse, S.F.B., 1791-1872 (Box 23)
    - Morton, Ree, 1936-1977 (Box 23)
    - Mozier, Joseph, 1812-1870 (Box 23)
    - Mundt, Ernst, 1905- (Box 23)
    - Murray, Robert, 1936- (Box 23)
    - Murray, Samuel, 1870-? (Box 23)
    - Myers, Forest, 1941- (Box 23)
    - Nadelman, Elie, 1885-1946 (Box 23)
    - Nagle, Ron (Box 23)
    - Nakian, Reuben, 1897- (Box 23)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1941- (Box 23)
      - Before-1966 (Box 23)
      - 1967 (Box 23)
      - 1968-1970 (Box 23)
      - 1971- (Box 23)
      - 1980- [Slide box 136] (Box 23)
    - Neri, Manuel, 1930- (Box 23)
    - Nevelson, Joyce (Box 23)
    - Nevelson, Louise, 1899-1988 (Box 23)
      - Before 1949 (Box 23)
      - 1950-1959 (Box 23)
      - 1960-1969 (Box 23)
      - 1970- (Box 23)
    - Newman, Barnett, 1905-1970 (Box 23)
      Xx for HERE I, 1950 see Painting U.S.- Newman, Barnett- The Wild,1950
    - Nickford, Juan, 1926- (Box 23)
    - Nivola, Costantino, 1911- (Box 23)
    - Noguchi, Isamu, 1904-1988 (Box 23)
      - Various titles [Slide boxes 136-137] (Box 23)
      - New York [Slide box 137] (Box 23)
    - Noland, Cady, 1956- (Box 23)
    - Nutt, James, 1938- (Box 23)
    - Oates, Daniel, 1964- (Box 23)
    - O'Connor, Andrew, 1874- (Box 23)
    - O'Hanion, Richard, 1906- (Box 23)
    - Oldenburg, Claes, 1929- (Box 23)
      Xx for "Balancing Tools" see Arch. 19th – 20th c. Germany- Weil am Rhein, Vitra Furniture Design Museum.
      - Before 1960 (Box 23)
      - 1961 (Box 23)
      - 1962 (Box 23)
      - 1963 (Box 23)
      - 1964 [Slide box 138] (Box 23)
      - 1965 (Box 23)
      - 1966 (Box 23)
      - 1967 (Box 23)
        - Drainpipes (Box 23)
      - 1968 (Box 23)
      - 1969 [Slide boxes 138-139] (Box 23–24)
        - Lipstick [Slide box 139] (Box 24)
      - 1970- (Box 24)
        - Lipstick (2nd version) (Box 24)
    - Olitski, Jules, 1922- (Box 24)
    - Olson, Eric (Box 24)
    - Opie, Julian (Box 24)
    - Oppenheim, Dennis, 1938- (Box 24)
      - Before 1979 (Box 24)
      - 1980- (Box 24)
    - Ortiz, Ralphael, 1934- (Box 24)
    - Osorio, Pepon, 1955- (Box 24)
    - Ossorio, Alfonso, 1916- (Box 24)
      Xx Painting U.S.
    - Otterness, Tom, 1952- (Box 24)
    - Otterson, Joel (Box 24)
    - Oursler, Tony, 1957- [Slide box 140] (Box 24)
    - Pacileo, Dolores, 1944- (Box 24)
    - Paine, Roxy, 1966- (Box 24)
    - Paik, Nam June, 1932- (Box 24)
    - Paley, Albert (Box 24)
    - Palmer, Erastus Dow, 1817-1904 (Box 24)
    - Patterson, Benjamin, act.c. 1960 (Box 24)
    - Pavia, Philip (Box 24)
    - Pepper, Beverly (Box 24)
    - Perkins, Marion, 1908-1961 (Box 24)
    - Persico, E. Luigi, 1791-1860 [Slide box 141] (Box 24)
    - Peskin, Roger (Box 24)
    - Pettrich, Ferdinand, 1798-1872 (Box 24)
    - Pfaff, Judy, 1946- (Box 24)
    - Phillips, Helen (Box 24)
    - Philpot, David, 1940- (Box 24)
    - Pierson, Jack, 1960- (Box 24)
    - Pineda, Marianna, 1925- (Box 24)
    - Pinto, Jody, 1942- (Box 24)
    - Piper, Adrian, 1948- (Box 24)
    - Pondick, Rona (Box 24)
    - Powers, Hiram, 1805-1873 (Box 24)
    - Pratt, Bella, 1867-1917 (Box 24)
    - Price, Kenneth, 1935- [Slide boxes 141-142] (Box 24)
    - Proctor, Alexander, 1862- [Slide box 142] (Box 24)
    - Prophet, Elizabeth (Box 24)
    - Puccinelli, Raymond (Box 24)
    - Puryear, Martin, 1941- (Box 24)
    - Quasius (Box 24)
    - Raemisch, Waldemar, 1888-1955 (Box 24)
    - Rainer, Yvonne, 1934- (Box 24)
    - Rammell, Reid (Box 24)
    - Rauschenberg, Robert, 1925- [Slide boxes 142-143] (Box 24)
    - Ray, Charles, 1953- [Slide box 143] (Box 24)
    - Reder, Bernard, 1897- (Box 24)
    - Reeves, Daniel, 1948- (Box 24)
    - Reimann, William, 1935- (Box 24)
    - Reichek, Elaine (Box 24)
    - Remington, Frederic, 1861-1909 (Box 24)
    - Rhoades, Jason, 1965- (Box 24)
    - Rhoden, John, 1918- (Box 24)
    - Rickey, George, 1907- (Box 24)
    - Rimmer, William, 1816-1879 (Box 24)
    - Rinehart, William Henry, 1825-1874 (Box 24)
    - Ringgold, Faith, 1934 (Box 24)
    - Rivers, Larry, 1923- (Box 24)
    - Robbins, David (Box 24)
    - Robus, Hugo, 1885-1964 (Box 24)
    - Rogers, John, 1829-1904 (Box 24)
    - Rogers, Randolph, 1825-1892 [Slide boxes 143-144] (Box 24)
    - Roosen, Mia Westerlund [Slide box 144] (Box 24)
    - Rosati, James, 1912- (Box 24)
    - Roseman, Harry (Box 24)
    - Rosenquist, James, 1933- (Box 24)
    - Rosenthal, Bernard, 1914- (Box 24)
    - Rosewald, Robert, 1920- (Box 24)
    - Rosler, Martha (Box 24)
    - Ross, Charles (Box 24)
    - Roszak, Theodore, 1907-1981 (Box 24)
    - Rothenberg, Erika, 1950- (Box 24)
    - Rox, Henry (Box 24)
    - Ruckstuhl, F. Wellington, 1853- (Box 24)
    - Rudy, Charles, 1904- (Box 24)
    - Rumsey, Charles, 1879-1922 (Box 24)
    - Rush, William, 1756-1833 [Slide boxes 144-145] (Box 24–25)
    - Ryman, Robert, 1930- [Slide box 145] (Box 25)
    - Saar, Alison, 1956- (Box 25)
    - Saar, Betye, 1926- (Box 25)
    - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus, 1848-1907 (Box 25)
      - Various Titles (Box 25)
      - Boston (Box 25)
      - New York [Slide boxes 145-146] (Box 25)
    - Saint Phalle, Niki de, 1930- [Slide box 146] (Box 25)
    - Samaras, Lucas, 1936 (Box 25)
      Xx Painting, Photography U.S.- Olderburg
      - Various titles (Box 25)
      - 1960-1969 (Box 25)
      - 1970-1979 (Box 25)
      - 1980-1989 (Box 25)
    - Sandback, Frederick Lane, 1943- (Box 25)
    - Saret, Alan, 1941- (Box 25)
    - Savage, Augusta, 1900-1962 (Box 25)
      Xx Arch. U.S., New York –Expositions- World's Fair 1939-1940
    - Saxe, Adrian (Box 25)
    - Scanga, Italo, 1932- (Box 25)
    - Scarpitta, Salvatore (Box 25)
    - Schamberg, Morton, 1881-1918 [Slide box 147] (Box 25)
    - Schaper, Ned (Box 25)
    - Schapiro, Miriam, 1923- (Box 25)
      Xx Woman House- Chicago, J.
    - Schmidt, Clarence (Box 25)
    - Schnabel, Day, 1905- (Box 25)
    - Schneemann, Carolee, 1939- (Box 25)
    - Schoebel, Harry (Box 25)
    - Schutte, Thomas, 1954- (Box 25)
    - Scott, Joyce J. (Box 25)
    - Segal, George, 1924- (Box 25)
      - Before 1962 (Box 25)
      - 1963 (Box 25)
      - 1964-1966 (Box 25)
      - 1967 (Box 25)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 25)
      - 1970- (Box 25)
    - Seley, Jason, 1919- (Box 25)
    - Serra, Richard, 1939- (Box 25)
      - 1967 (Box 25)
      - 1968 [Slide boxes 147-148] (Box 25)
      - 1969 [Slide box 148] (Box 25)
      - 1970-1979 (Box 25)
      - 1980- (Box 25)
    - Shapiro, Joel, 1941- (Box 25)
    - Sharits, Paul (Box 25)
    - Shaw, Richard, 1941- (Box 25)
    - Shiraga Kazuo, 1924- (Box 25)
    - Shu Lea Cheang, 1954- (Box 25)
    - Simkhovitch, Helena, 1908- (Box 25)
    - Simmons, Gary, 1964- (Box 25)
    - Simonds, Charles, 1945- (Box 25)
    - Simpson, Tommy [Slide box 149] (Box 25)
    - Simpson, Lorna, 1961- (Box 25)
    - Singer, Michael (Box 25)
    - Silverthorne, Jeanne (Box 25)
    - Skillin, Simeon Jr. (Box 25)
    - Skoglund, Sandy (Box 25)
      Xx Photography and Painting
    - Slivka, David (Box 25)
    - Smith, Alexis, 1949- (Box 25)
    - Smith, David, 1906-1965 (Box 25)
      - Various titles (Box 25)
      - Before 1937 (Box 25)
      - 1938-1944 (Box 25)
      - 1945-1950 (Box 25)
      - 1951-1955 [Slide box 150] (Box 25)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 25)
      - 1958-1960 (Box 25)
      - 1961 (Box 25)
      - 1962 (Box 25)
      - 1963 (Box 25)
      - 1964-1965 [Slide box 151] (Box 26)
    - Smith, Frank E. (Box 26)
    - Smith, Kiki, 1954- (Box 26)
    - Smith, Tony, 1912-1981 (Box 26)
      Xx for House Design-Architecture U.S.
    - Smithson, Robert, 1938-1973 (Box 26)
      - Various titles (Box 26)
      - Before 1966 (Box 26)
      - 1967-1969 [Slide boxes 151-152] (Box 26)
      - 1970- [Slide box 152] (Box 26)
    - Smyth, Ned, 1948- (Box 26)
    - Snelson, Kenneth, 1927- (Box 26)
    - Snyder, Kit-Yin, act.c.1980 (Box 26)
    - Sonfist, Alan, 1948- (Box 26)
    - Sonnier, Keith, 1941- (Box 26)
    - Sorenson, Margrete (Box 26)
    - Sorrells-Adewale, E.H (Box 26)
    - Spaventa, George, 1918- (Box 26)
    - Spero, Nancy (Box 26)
    - Sperry, Ann (Box 26)
    - Squier, Jack, 1927- (Box 26)
    - Stackhouse, Robert, 1942- (Box 26)
    - Stankiewicz, Richard, 1922-1983 [Slide boxes 152-153] (Box 26)
    - Stea, Cesare [Slide box 153] (Box 26)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1944- (Box 26)
    - Steinberg, Saul, 1914- (Box 26)
    - Steiner, Michael (Box 26)
    - Stella, Frank, 1936- (Box 26)
    - Stephenson, Peter, 1823-c.1860 (Box 26)
    - Sterne, Maurice, 1877-1957 (Box 26)
    - Stockholder, Jessica, 1959- (Box 26)
    - Stoliar, Lee (Box 26)
    - Stone, Sylvia (Box 26)
    - Storrs, J.B., 1885-1956 (Box 26)
    - Story, William Wetmore, 1819-1895 (Box 26)
    - Stout, Renee, 1958- (Box 26)